officekb.com 2006-03-13

# Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices, including how we collect and use the information you may provide to us on the site, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where we request personally identifiable information. This statement may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page to remain fully informed of our commitment. 

**What information we collect and how we use it**

We ask you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service. Please note:

  * We do not rent, sell or share your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent, are required by law, or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of OfficeKB.com or its users. 
  * If you have an account, we may use the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. 
  * We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information with others. Examples of this include the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement.

We use the information we gather for three general purposes:

  * To enhance the user experience in our network of sites. 
  * To fulfill your requests for certain services, such as enabling users to participate in newsgroup discussions. 
  * To send you information you agreed to receive.

**Cookies**

In order to personalize and enhance your experience on our Web site, we also may collect information through "cookies". Cookies are small strings of text that are sent by our site to your Web browser and then stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:

  * Saving your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites 
  * Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies are necessary to provide you with certain features such as posting to the discussion groups.

**Discussion groups**

Our website give you full access to the related newsgroup discussions. It eliminates the need for newsreading software and lets you post your comments to an existing newsgroup or search the newsgroup archive in the same way you would search HTML pages on the Internet.

Please note: You acknowledge that all the discussion groups are public and not private communications, and that therefore others may read your communications without your knowledge. Always use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about yourself in your posting. Any communication that you post to the Service is considered to be non-confidential.

**_We do not recommend posting your email address in the discussion forum messages_** as it might be collected by the people who harvest the emails from websites, include them into mailing lists, and send unsolicited emails (SPAM).

**Privacy of children**

Our Web sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our sites in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. This requirement is clearly posted during the registration process.

**Links to third party Web sites**

Our sites offer hyperlinks to other Web sites which may have information policies and practices different from ours. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of any third party Web sites.

**Questions and comments**

Questions regarding this privacy statement should be submitted via the feedback form. We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to every one.
